evanmarckatz.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy - Dating Coach - Evan Marc Katz | Understand Men. Find Love.

We at evanmarckatz.com respect the privacy concerns of the users of this site and have created this privacy policy to explain (1) what information we gather from you when you visit our site, (2) how we may use such information, (3) your choices concerning how we may use such information and (4) the security measures we take to protect such information. Some information is collected on this site automatically through our technology; other information is collected only when you choose to give it to us (e.g., when you purchase our services or sign up for a specific online transaction).

_**Information We Gather Automatically**_  
When you visit this site, certain non-personally identifying information is recorded automatically by the standard operation of our Internet servers. Information such as the type of browser being used, its operating system, and your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address (a number that your Internet service provider assigns to your computer whenever you surf the Internet) is gathered in order to facilitate our online operations and to assure an efficient online experience for you. We may also use or share this information for security purposes, to generate group statistics about our user community, or as required by law.

We may use your IP address or other automatically recorded information, in cooperation with your Internet provider, to identify you if it is necessary to contact you or to bring legal action against you because you are violating the Terms and Conditions of use for this site or may be causing injury to or interference (intentionally or unintentionally) with our company’s rights or property, other users of this site or anyone else who could be harmed by your activities.

We allow third-party companies, including AddThis, to collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or a third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org.

_**Personal Information You Provide To Us**_  
We may request personally identifying information from you in a variety of contexts. For example, you may provide such data to us if you: (1) purchase any products or services from evanmarckatz.com; (2) fill out an order form to request information; (3) register to participate in community features; or (4) complete an online registration form (e.g., various sign-up forms for receiving email newsletters, registering for special offers, registering for an account, entering a contest or responding to a survey).

In such cases, the personally identifying information we request may include your name, email address, mailing address and zip code, phone number, and, where appropriate, a valid credit card number with expiration date (collectively, “Personal Information”). In addition, we may collect other non-personally identifying information such as your date of birth, gender, country of residence, hobbies, interests and other information regarding your interaction with our site, preferences and other customized activities in which you participate. Of course, you never have to answer any of the questions we ask you or otherwise interact with our site and/or our consultants, but refusal to do so may limit the products or services we can offer or provide to you.

_**How Can Your Personal Information Be Used?**_

_Within evanmarckatz.com_  
When you purchase products or services from evanmarckatz.com, we will use your Personal Information to fulfill your order and for customer service. Many online customers are particularly concerned about their credit card information, which we will share only as required by companies involved in your transaction (e.g., fulfillment, billing, mailing, storage or delivery services). We will not share your credit card information with any other company unless it is involved in the fulfillment or delivery of your order. We do not rent, sell or share credit card information with promotional partners or other third parties.

We may use your Personal Information and other non-personally identifying information we collect to update you about our products or services or to contact you about offers of new evanmarckatz.com products or services that are of interest to you. You always have the option to receive fewer or no communications in the future from us by opting out. You may opt out by following the instructions included in the specific communication you no longer wish to receive or by sending an email to support@evanmarckatz.com and explaining how you would like to modify your preferences.

_**For Legal Enforcement Purposes**_  
We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information, including credit card information, as required by law or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against you if you are violating the Terms and Conditions of use for this site or may be causing injury to or interference (intentionally or unintentionally) with our company’s rights or property, other users of this site or anyone else who could be harmed by your activities.

_**Safeguarding Your Personal Information**_  
evanmarckatz.com cares about the security of your Personal Information. We follow generally accepted industry security standards to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use such Personal Information. However, unfortunately, despite many advances in information security technology and procedures, no commercially deployed method of information transfer over the Internet or electronic data storage is known to be 100% secure. As a result, while we do strive to use modern and commercially reasonable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of that information during its transmission or its storage in our systems.

_**Cookies**_  
A “cookie” is a small text file that an Internet site can place on your computer’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make using this site easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you, keeping track of your shopping cart when you visit our online store or other similar purposes, and to help identify you whenever you return to our site, so you do not need to reenter your identification information.

Most Internet browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. However, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to alert you when a cookie is being sent (note: you may need to consult your browser’s “Help” area for instructions on how to do that). If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie, some parts of this site will not function properly or may perform considerably slower. For example, without cookies, you will not be able to set personalized preferences or you may have difficulty completing shopping transactions, listening to music or playing games.

**_First, what is a cookie?_  
**A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that I/we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer. You can find more information about web cookies here: <https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie>

**We use the following cookies:**

  * **Strictly necessary cookies.**  These are cookies that are required for you to use the features available on this website. They include, for example, the ability to login and post a comment.
  * **Analytical/performance cookies.**  These cookies allow us to recognize, track, and count the number of visitors who come to this website. They also allow us to track broken pages on the website and to count what visitors do when they click through the website.
  * **Functionality cookies.**  These cookies allow us to track and remember your preferences for our website. For example, we can personalized content for you, greet you by name and/or remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).

We use two different kinds of cookies on this website: First party and third-party cookies (both defined in detail on the wikipedia link above).

**First-party cookies**  
These cookies are specifically about www.thewideawakening.com and soul.thewideawakening.com and track your usage of this website. These cookies are considered essential for the website to operate correctly. These cookies, none of which capture personally identifiable information, include:

  * Visitor ID – this cookie is a numeric value that identifies unique visitors and provides coherence and consistency to a site visit- it is anonymous and contains no personally identifying information;
  * Page number – this cookie identifies the page you are on;
  * Session ID – this cookie identifies your website session;
  * Test – this cookie checks whether or not your browser supports cookies;

**Third-party cookies**  
This website sets different types of third-party cookies to track usage, social sharing and more. These cookies are not under my/our control, and serve to help us understand the visitors who come to the website, as well as support our connection to other third party sites. (Again, see the wikipedia page above for detailed explanations of third party services/cookies).

**Included in our list of third-party cookies are the following services:**

  * **Google Analytics**  –Google Analytics is used to collect data about website usage. This data does not include personally identifiable information. You can view the Google Privacy Policy here: www.google.com/policies/privacy/.
  * **Social Sharing** – a cookie is used when you use the social sharing service on our website to share a link with LinkedIn, Facebook, Twitter, etc. More information about the Sharing app privacy policy can be found here: https://jetpack.com/support/sharing/#privacy under the Site Visitors sections.
  * **Facebook**  –a Facebook pixel may be used to obtain information regarding the activities that users engage in while visiting our web pages. For information on Facebook’s Privacy and Cookie policy, visit https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/
  * **Blog Comments** – If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

**Your rights  **with **  cookies:**  
Cookies are set by many entities and may include the website’s owners/developers/managers, plugins, third-party providers, advertisers and anyone else who collects or uses the website’s data.

As a user of this (or any) website, you can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of some, or all cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of the site.

To learn how to block cookies, simply go to Google and type in “how do I block cookies” on whatever browser you use (Chrome, Firefox etc.) and you will find the details needed to block some or all cookies on your browser.

**Additional data storage and privacy policy considerations**  
In addition to the non-personally identifiable data collected by cookies, this website also offers the ability to contact with us via contact forms, newsletter registration forms, downloadable ebooks, free downloadable gifts, webinars and other similar files.

To receive free gifts from this website, we require that you share your personal information consisting of your first and last name and your email address. In some cases we have additional optional fields. In most cases, information is gathered and stored in the website database or via a third-party service like Infusionsoft. All information gathered via any form on this website can be deleted upon request.

Information and informational items are provided in exchange for adding your email address and possibly your name, business and or website information to one of our mailing lists. All mailing lists are stored and executed via Infusionsoft for the sole purpose of communicating information, as well as occasional marketing of services and products. Each mailing list will specifically detail what type of emails you may receive and possibly the frequency. You may unsubscribe from said email list(s) at any time by using the unsubscribe link provided in every email.

_**ADDITIONAL:**_

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behave in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

When visitors leave comments on the site, the data collection form collects the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue. Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

**_Copyright Information_  
**Some images on evanmarckatz.com are readily available in various places on the Internet and believed to be in public domain. Images posted are believed to be posted within our rights according to the U.S. Copyright Fair Use Act (title 17, U.S. Code.)

**_Claims of Infringement_  
**If you believe that any content appearing on evanmarckatz.com infringes on your copyright, please let us know. E-Mail support@evanmarckatz.com with following information to us and the infringing material will be removed as soon as possible.

(a) your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address;  
(b) a description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;  
(c) the exact URL or a description of each place where alleged infringing material is located;  
(d) a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use has not been authorized by you, your agent, or the law;  
(e) your electronic or physical signature or the electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on your behalf; and  
(f) a statement by you made under penalty of perjury, that the information in your notice is accurate, that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf

Please also note that under Section 512(f) of the Copyright Act any person who knowingly materially misrepresents that material or activity is infringing may be subject to liability.

_**How to Contact Us**_  
If you have any questions or complaints about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@evanmarckatz.com. When we receive such inquiries about our Privacy Policy, we will use the Personal Information (such as your email address) only to respond to your question or comment. However, if your question raises one or more issues that affect our promotional partners, we may also share your question with them in order to provide a response.

_**Changes in This Privacy Policy**_  
We reserve the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we make changes which we consider material in our privacy practices, we will notify you in this space. We may also attempt to notify you of any such material changes to our privacy practices via email or by placing a notice on our home page.

_**Acceptance of This Privacy Policy**_  
By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of your Personal Information by evanmarckatz.com in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

© 2018 evanmarckatz.com, All rights reserved.
